Yesterday,
you were so full of yourself
when you smashed my goods.
What?
Today, you're here asking for help?
Fine.
We've known each other for many years.
=Cases Between Us=
I will help you.
But I have
one condition.
=Episode 34=
One favor
for one question.
Yesterday, you smashed this vase
and said it was fake.
Today, in front of everyone,
I'd like you to judge it again.
You want the truth?
I want to hear
whatever you choose to say.
It's genuine.
What?
Isn't this the same vase from yesterday?
Young Master Zhao, he...
It's genuine?
But you said it was fake.
Take another look.
No need.
It's genuine.
Young Master Zhao,
I thought you never got it wrong.
It's obviously a fake.
How did you come to that conclusion?
How about this one?
Go on.
It's genuine.
Wrong.
It's fake.
If you keep passing off
fakes as genuine,
how are you ever going to survive
in Liulichang Antique Market?
My knowledge is shallow.
I'm shortsighted.
I've been talking nonsense
about every piece
that has passed through my hands.
My apologies.
Apologies?
Just flapping your gums is enough?
Well, well.
You've been standing
on your high horse for too long.
Is that really
how you ask someone for a favor?
Walk out that door,
and you'll never know
where those imperial antiques went.
Come on.
Young Master Zhao.
You really know how
to swallow your pride.
But you're thinking too simply.
Liulichang Antique Market
isn't the only place
that deals in antiques.
What are you getting at?
Like I said,
one favor,
one question.
What more do you want?
Still got some backbone, huh?
He actually came.
Young Master Zhao,
if you can take
these eight welcoming rods
and crawl to my feet,
I'll count that
as your second favor.
What?
Lost your nerve?
If you're scared, go home.
Right!
- Go home!
Young Master Zhao.
Afraid?
If this is all the sincerity you've got.
Show him out.
- Go home!
I told you.
He chickened out.
What a waste of time.
He knelt.
This rascal.
Hit him harder.
Young Master Zhao has thick skin.
Right, everyone?
- Yeah!
- Harder!
He's coughing up blood.
He's bleeding.
Everyone.
Take a good look.
This is Young Master Zhao who once
ruled Liulichang Antique Market.
Look at him now.
How is he any different from a stray dog?
- Exactly!
- He's a stray.
Look at him.
Good for him.
He really took it.
Right.
I didn't expect that.
- He held on.
He really did.
Young Master Zhao.
Closer.
To be honest,
I never
realized that
you had
such backbone.
But your knees
are pretty soft.
Wouldn't you say?
- That's right.
You're too naive.
I only said you could ask.
I never said I would answer.
Isn't that right,
everyone?
- That's right.
- That's right!
Exactly, he never said that.
Nice!
This feels great!
Let's go and have some tea.
Let's go.
Come on.
Move.
(Pleasures of Pottery and Fishing)
Stop.
Isn't this Young Master Zhao?
Have a rough day?
Si, give Young Master Zhao a hand.
Master Liang,
good day.
You look to be
in high spirits today.
Young Master Zhao,
that's not quite fair.
Back then, when you ruined
other people's business
and embarrassed them,
weren't you just riding the tide, too?
You can't blame me
just because the wind has changed
and you've fallen from your pedestal.
Since you know the wind can change,
you also know
it begins with the slightest breeze.
East wind or west,
who knows
which way it will blow tomorrow?
Young Master Zhao,
do you know why,
of all the spoiled rich guys in Beijing,
I like you the most?
Because you see things clearly.
You're right.
Once the wind changes,
no one knows where it will blow.
That's why I never corner people.
I came today to tell you this.
You won't find those imperial antiques
in Liulichang Antique Market.
What...
What do you mean?
I'm a man
who appreciates atmosphere.
Nothing beats a lone fortress
against the setting sun.
If you want the best view
in Beijing,
go to the old watchtower
at the Weng City.
Young Master Zhao,
if you're in the mood tonight,
take a walk up there.
You might see
something worth seeing.
Since when are you this kind?
I have parents to care for
and children to raise.
Seeing how desperate you are
to save your father,
I couldn't help but feel for you.
Think of it as earning a little virtue.
Believe me or not, that's up to you.
Funny world, isn't it?
Today it's the east wind.
Tomorrow, the west.
Yet, somehow the wind
never blows my way.
That's because
you're good at playing the game.
In this life,
people chase fame,
fortune,
honor,
or love.
Try to have them all,
and you'll end up with none.
There's a blade
beside the character "profit."
It cuts down those blinded by greed.
Yang,
how many years
have you been with the department?
Commissioner,
eight years.
Before Yuan Hong left,
he specifically recommended you.
Do you know
why I only made you
acting chief?
The key to being an official
is knowing the ropes.
When to reach out
and when to stay well away,
you need to be clear.
You may not understand that yet.
That's alright.
As for the rest,
it depends on how quickly you learn.
♪Good folks♪
♪Bad folks♪
♪None should wear the begonia♪
(Serve the People
with Loyalty and Integrity)
- Get to work!
- Move!
Who are you?
Lost your mind?
Zhao?
What happened to you?
Do me a favor.
I really can't help
with your father's case.
He was framed.
Those missing imperial antiques
still haven't surfaced on the market.
Tonight,
a shipment of antiques
is being moved through the city gate.
I think something's off.
I need to borrow a few men
to come with me to the watchtower.
The Commissioner
has been watching me like a hawk.
He just lectured me,
saying he'd be observing my performance.
Fine.
Thanks.
Hold on.
How many men do you need?
Two plainclothes teams...
Shouldn't we report this to...
Buddy,
let's go.
I'll help you, even if I lose my job.
(End of Episode 34)
♪Side by side,
we journey through this life♪
♪Troubled times
are but a laughing matter♪
♪However, the world changes♪
♪You'll still be by my side♪
♪Side by side,
we journey through this life♪
♪Praise and blame come and go♪
♪If this is my final chapter♪
♪I'll solve this mystery with you♪